<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<workflow xmlns="http://eprints.org/ep3/workflow" xmlns:epp="http://eprints.org/ep3/phrase" xmlns:epc="http://eprints.org/ep3/control">
  <flow>
    <stage ref="main"/>
  </flow>
  <stage name="main">
    <component type="XHTML">
      <h3 style="text-align:center">How to use EASY PAGES</h3>

      <p>You may wish to create a new page for many reasons; announcements, documentation, instructions, further details, etc.</p>
      <p>With the easy pages tool you can easily create a page to provide information.</p>
      <p><b>1.</b> Provide a title for the page, this will appear at the top of the page as a heading.</p>

      <p><b>2.</b> Provide a language for the page, if this EPrints instance is multi-lingual.</p>
      <p><b>3.</b> Add the page contents and use the document formatting tool to organise the information appropriately.</p>
      <p><b>4.</b> Lastly, enter a path name. This will be the repository's URL with <code>/page/the-name-you-choose</code> appended.</p>
      <h4>Multiple Languages</h4>
      <p>Multiple languages can be supported by adding multiple pages with the same path, and different language. The best available path for the current language will be displayed to the user.</p>
      
      <p>For example, for a multi-lingual information page, create two pages with the same path ("information" for the default information page) each in a different language (for example, English and German). When a user has configured EPrints to be in English the information page in English will be presented at /page/information. When Eprints is configured in German, the german information page will be presented at /page/information. Any extra pages with the same path in the same language will be ignored.</p>
      <br/>
      <p>Once you have finished you can click Save and Return, this will provide you with a link to the finished page.</p>
      <p>Use the link just as you would use a normal URL link. For example, it could be added to the repository home page, added to a workflow field description, sent out in an email etc.</p>
      <p><b>Pages can be managed via <a href="/cgi/users/home?screen=Listing&amp;dataset=page">'Manage records > Pages'</a>.  This is limited to Admin users only.</b></p>
      <p><b>All created pages are public.  A list of pages can be accessed via <a href="{$config{https_root}}/pages.html">REPO-URL/pages.html</a></b></p>
      <br/>
      <h3>Dynamic variables available to you:</h3>

      <p>Type placeholders when you want dynamic values shown in their place.</p>

      <p>Use the placeholders anywhere you would like dynamic content to appear.</p>
      <p>You can preview the dynamic content using View-&gt;Preview on the menubar, or the Preview icon on the toolbar.</p>

      <table>
          <tr>
              <td>Placeholder</td>
              <td>Current value</td>
              <td>Where Value is Defined:</td>
          </tr>
          <tr>
              <td>PUT-ADMIN-EMAIL-HERE</td>
              <td><epc:print expr='$config{adminemail}' /></td>
              <td>Repository Configuration</td>
          </tr>
          <tr>
              <td>PUT-ARCHIVE-NAME-HERE</td>
              <td><epc:phrase ref="archive_name"/></td>
              <td>Phrase Editor</td>
          </tr>
          <tr>
              <td>PUT-ARCHIVE-URL-HERE</td>
              <td><epc:print expr='$config{https_root}' /></td><!-- Not honest - as archive url is actually a value calculated in z_pages.pl 
                                                                - this is simply close enough until can be improved to have parity.
                                                                Also potentially displays blank if no https.
                                                                Could be improved with test conditionals and alternatives-->
              <td>Repository Configuration</td>
          </tr>
          <tr>
              <td>PUT-CGI-URL-HERE</td>
              <td><epc:print expr='$config{perl_url}' /></td><!-- Not honest - as cgi url is actually a value calculated in z_pages.pl - this is simply close enough - this is simply close enough until can be improved to have parity.-->
              <td>Repository Configuration</td>
          </tr>
      </table>

      <br/>

      <h3>Instant Substitutions:</h3>

      <p>Type instant substitutions when you want something to appear instantly.</p>

      <p>These are essentially convenient shortcuts.</p>

      <table>
          <tr>
              <td>Typing this...</td>
              <td>Does this...</td>
          </tr>
          <tr>
              <td>INSTANT-ADMIN-EMAIL-LINK</td>
              <td>Creates an admin email link.</td>
          </tr>
          <tr>
              <td>INSTANT-ARCHIVE-LINK</td>
              <td>Creates an archive link.</td>
          </tr>
      </table>

      <p>Where these also use placeholders, you can preview their dynamic content using View-&gt;Preview on the menubar, or the Preview icon on the toolbar.</p>

    </component>
    <component>
      <field ref="title"/>
    </component>
    <component>
      <field ref="language"/>
    </component>
    <component>
      <field ref="payload"/>
    </component>
    <component show_help="always">
      <field ref="path" input_lookup_url="{$config{rel_cgipath}}/users/lookup/easy_pages_paths"/>
    </component>
  </stage>
</workflow>
